dinkleboo.com 2016-12-01

# Privacy Policy - Personalised Kids Stuff

## Dinkleboo and Your Right to Privacy

Dinkleboo is committed to protecting your privacy and will always act to protect your information. On December 21, 2001 new legislative provisions came into force which governs the way organisations hold and handle personal information. This Privacy Policy sets out how Dinkleboo collects and uses personal information, and how you can access personal information that we keep. 

## Why Dinkleboo Collects Personal Information

  * Selling, promoting and provision of products, services and membership requested by you.
  * Registering and handling of product warranties.
  * Providing you with information that you request (by post, telephone, fax or email).
  * Sending you additional information on Dinkleboo products, services and promotions which we think may be of interest to you.
  * Sending you information on products and services of our select business partners that we think may be of interest to you (if by email, only where appropriate or where you have opted in).

You can request not to receive this additional information by contacting us as detailed below. If you do not wish to provide Dinkleboo with personal information, we will be unable to properly provide you with the products, services and information that you request. 

## Protection of your Email Address

Dinkleboo does not make your email address available to any third parties. Your email address is used by Dinkleboo to provide you with the Dinkleboo Home Ordering Service, and to send you special offers, gold club mailings and updates on new Dinkleboo services we think will be of interest to you. If you do not wish to receive such emails, you can "opt out" or unsubscribe to these emails at anytime. To "opt out" click "unsubscribe" at the bottom of your email, or use the unsubscribe function either when you supply your personal information to Dinkleboo via this website or when you receive additional information from us. You will still receive Order Confirmation emails, when using the Dinkleboo Home Ordering Service. 

## Disclosure of Personal Information

To assist in providing some products and services, Dinkleboo may pass on your personal information and your requested delivery information to other organisations in Australia. These organisations have compliant privacy procedures in place and must not use your personal information for any other purpose. Dinkleboo may occasionally disclose personal information to its related companies as defined by the Corporations Law but, wherever possible, this information is disclosed in a depersonalised format. Dinkleboo may develop general reports incorporating some personal information in a depersonalised format for use by our business partners. Dinkleboo may collect identifiable information from visits to our website to help us provide better customer service through the use of various technologies, including "cookies". A cookie is a piece of data that a website can send to your browser which may then be stored on your computer as a tag that identifies your computer and /or the computer user. Such technologies enable Dinkleboo to measure and analyse, for example, visitor activity on the website, visits to web pages and the domains from which people visit. This information assists Dinkleboo in understanding trends and patterns and helps to serve you better when you return to the website or when a new product or service becomes available. You can set your browser to notify you before you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it. You can also set your browser to turn off cookies. If you turn off cookies, there may be some features and pages of Dinkleboo's site that will not display properly to you. You can find out about cookies at the following website:- 

Other than described above, Dinkleboo will not use, sell or disclose your personal information without your consent. Security of your Personal Information Dinkleboo holds all personal information securely. Access is restricted to the Dinkleboo employees who need the personal information for a designated purpose and additional security measures including secure locked areas, the highest level of commercially available encryption for financial transactions on line and secure disposal procedures have been implemented. Access to your Personal Information You have a right to access the personal information Dinkleboo collects about you. If you wish to access or change your personal information, or have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us. Attention: Privacy Officer, Dinkleboo Australia. 

_**The Privacy Officer  
Dinkleboo Australia. **_
